hi this is Cambria from the Federation
for children with special needs and the
Massachusetts statewide family
engagement Center this video will help
you learn how to access zoom this could
be helpful for many of you as your
children may be expected to use zoom to
meet with their classmates or teacher
during our school closings your child
should get an invitation that looks
something like this
saying please join my zoom meeting you
can call in by phone by dialing these
numbers and entering the meeting ID code
or you can click on the link to access
zoom online we're going to open zoom
meetings
and you'll see that there is a preview
of what your video will look like you
can choose to join with video if you
want your face on a screen or your
child's face on the screen or you can
join without video we're going to join
without video to begin with you can join
with computer audio and you can test
your speaker and microphone first if you
like now I'm using my computer's audio
you can see my name and you can see the
name of the person who organized this
meeting for us who's also online they
can hear me right now because my
microphone is on and you can see the
green light moving up and down as I talk
I can start my video and they'll be able
to see me
can you hear me and now I can mute
myself and he can't hear me any longer
inside the zoom platform you'll see
there's some other options at the bottom
you can invite other people you'll see
that there are two participants in this
zoom meeting I can share my screen if I
click on this I can choose something to
share and everyone can see the last
PowerPoint I was working on I can share
something new
and I can stop this year I can also chat
with everyone in the meeting or with
just one person this is a private chat
we can record the meeting here and we
can add reactions this is the speaker
view the person who's speaking is
highlighted we can also go to gallery
view and if there are multiple people
you'll see them all lined up when you're
done with your meeting you simply click
leave a meeting by and you're done I
hope this has been helpful